var words = 
[
    {
        "question": "الَّذِينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "alladhīna",
        "frequency": "1464",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اللَّهِ",
        "answer": "(of) Allah",
        "pcklId": "147",
        "tlit": "l-lahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "لِلَّهِ",
        "answer": "(be) to Allah",
        "pcklId": "148",
        "tlit": "lillahi",
        "frequency": "2851",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْحَمْدُ",
        "answer": "All praises and thanks",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "al-ḥamdu",
        "frequency": "63",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الدِّينِ",
        "answer": "(of the) Judgment",
        "pcklId": "2",
        "tlit": "l-dīni",
        "frequency": "101",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "رَبِّ",
        "answer": "the Lord",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "rabbi",
        "frequency": "980",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنِ",
        "answer": "the Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "90",
        "tlit": "l-raḥmāni",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحْمَٰنِ",
        "answer": "The Most Gracious",
        "pcklId": "91",
        "tlit": "al-raḥmāni",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "216",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmi",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الرَّحِيمِ",
        "answer": "the Most Merciful",
        "pcklId": "217",
        "tlit": "l-raḥīmi",
        "frequency": "339",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "3"
    },
    {
        "question": "بِسْمِ",
        "answer": "In (the) name",
        "pcklId": "8",
        "tlit": "bis'mi",
        "frequency": "381",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "1"
    },
    {
        "question": "الصِّرَاطَ",
        "answer": "(to) the path",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "l-ṣirāṭa",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "صِرَاطَ",
        "answer": "(The) path",
        "pcklId": "1",
        "tlit": "ṣirāṭa",
        "frequency": "45",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الضَّالِّينَ",
        "answer": "(of) those who go astray",
        "pcklId": "173",
        "tlit": "l-ḍālīna",
        "frequency": "191",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَعْبُدُ",
        "answer": "we worship",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "naʿbudu",
        "frequency": "275",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْعَالَمِينَ",
        "answer": "of the universe",
        "pcklId": "476",
        "tlit": "l-ʿālamīna",
        "frequency": "854",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "2"
    },
    {
        "question": "نَسْتَعِينُ",
        "answer": "we ask for help",
        "pcklId": "4",
        "tlit": "nastaʿīnu",
        "frequency": "11",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "5"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمَغْضُوبِ",
        "answer": "those who earned (Your) wrath",
        "pcklId": "22",
        "tlit": "l-maghḍūbi",
        "frequency": "24",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "غَيْرِ",
        "answer": "not (of)",
        "pcklId": "5",
        "tlit": "ghayri",
        "frequency": "154",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "الْمُسْتَقِيمَ",
        "answer": "the straight",
        "pcklId": "646",
        "tlit": "l-mus'taqīma",
        "frequency": "660",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "مَالِكِ",
        "answer": "(The) Master",
        "pcklId": "202",
        "tlit": "māliki",
        "frequency": "206",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "4"
    },
    {
        "question": "أَنْعَمْتَ",
        "answer": "You have bestowed (Your) Favors",
        "pcklId": "19",
        "tlit": "anʿamta",
        "frequency": "140",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "7"
    },
    {
        "question": "اهْدِنَا",
        "answer": "Guide us",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "ih'dinā",
        "frequency": "316",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "6"
    },
    {
        "question": "يَوْمِ",
        "answer": "(of the) Day",
        "pcklId": "0",
        "tlit": "yawmi",
        "frequency": "405",
        "surah": "1",
        "ayah": "4"
    }
]; 
export default words;